Allows you to select one of four game modes at the race selection stage (2 days). Race the red player near the red crystals, the blue player near the blue crystals.
1. You can choose any race to play. To select random races, the red player must approach the mummy.
2. Players sort matchups from unwanted to favorable, and then automatically selects the most preferred for both.
3. Players first form four intermediate matchups, and then draw two of them. Of the remaining two matchups randomly selected one.
4. The players strike the sets, the characters, whom or against whom do not wish to play. At the first stage, the upper or lower set is crossed out, at the second stage, the left or right set of the opponent is crossed out. After this form of 4 possible matchup, and each player strikes an unwanted matchup.