Unique Ranger's skill. Allows Ranger to choose 1 favored enemy from creatures 1 - 7 tier in the Avengers Guild. All Ranger's troops will receive a 40% chance to inflict a critical hit upon that creature, giving double damage to it. In addition, the damage to creatures from direct Ranger attacks increases - when calculating damage, the hero's level is considered high by +3, and if a creature is present in the Ranger's list of sworn enemies, the damage is doubled, and at least one creature always dies after that.